Microsoft the owner of Windows
has published 1 study that smells like a manual
of instructions of 1 IKEA cabinet
no one reads it but you should
analyzed professionals who use
ia every day and they discovered
something very important
and the more they trust in GPT chat
the less they think
ia has solved their lives
but it has also deleted their criteria
this is called surrender
December and the good news is that it has a cure
challenge for this week
when the ia gives you 1 answer
ask yourself this question
what is missing if you don't know what to answer congratulations
have you discovered that you also live in zombie mode?